{"tossups": [{"question": "<em>A ruler of this city built the fortress of Ortygia.</em> During a festival to Artemis, this city was captured by Marcus Claudius Marcellus after a protracted siege. A general from this city named Hicetas took control of this city, only to be removed from power by Timoleon. Two tyrants name Dionysius ruled this city, which was home to a scientist who supposedly built a giant claw and heat ray to defend it. For 10 points, name this home of Archimedes, a city on Sicily.", "answer": "<b><u>Syracuse</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em>This scandal was initially prosecuted by General John Brooks Henderson, who was later</em> <em>dismissed</em>. A trial stemming from this scandal forced the St. Louis courtroom to be expanded to fit all the reporters. It involved General Orville Babcock, who was eventually exposed by Secretary of the Treasury Benjamin Bristow. For 10 points, name this scandal for the Grant administration in which federal tax revenues on liquor were illegally diverted.", "answer": "<b><u>Whiskey Ring</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>This king drove back attempts by another nation's Henry III to invade France, including at the</em> <em>Battle of Taillebourg.</em> This king's brother Robert of Artois was killed during a battle at Al-Mansurah, which was fought after the capture of Damietta. This king commissioned the construction of the Sainte-Chapelle, in which he placed the Crown of Thorns. This son of Blanche of Castile participated in the Seventh and Eighth Crusades. For 10 points, name this canonized French king.", "answer": "<b><u>Louis IX</u></b> [or <b><u>Saint Louis</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em>This man's leadership was the subject of the bookA State of Blood</em>. This leader's health minister, Henry Kyemba, defected to the U.K. He was served by Bob Astles, the \"White Rat.\" This leader took power in a coup begun while President Milton Obote (<b>pr. oh-BOE-tay</b>) was out of the country.This man expelled 60,000 South Asians from his country in 1972 and lost power in a failed war with Tanzania. For 10 points, name this dictator of Uganda who was deposed in 1979.", "answer": "Idi <b><u>Amin</u></b> Dada  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>It's not Kentucky, but a movie about a team from this state featured Jon Voight as Coach</em> <em>Adolph Rupp</em>. A team from this state was the focus of the film <em>Glory Road</em>, starring Josh Lucas as Coach Don Haskins.A university from this state defeated Kentucky in 1966 to mark the first time that a college basketball team with five black starters won a title. For 10 points, name this Southern state where the school that is now the UTEP Miners plays games in El Paso.", "answer": "<b><u>Texas</u></b> [or <b><u>Texas</u></b> Western]  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>Arthur Krock helped lead the lobbying efforts for this book to win the Pulitzer Prize.</em> It was written while the author was recovering from back surgery, and columnist Drew Pearson claimed that Ted Sorenson actually wrote this book. This book looks at Edmund Ross, who broke party lines to vote for acquittal during Andrew Johnson's impeachment. For 10 points, name this collection of short biographies of U.S. Senators written by John F. Kennedy.", "answer": "<em><b><u>Profiles in Courage</u></b></em>  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>This event resulted in a brief arrest of Guillaume Apollinaire.</em> This action was first brought to attention by Louis Beroud. It was resolved when an ad by Alfredo Geri found its way to investigators. This action was carried out by hiding in a closet overnight, then hiding the central painting inside under artist's smocks. It was perpetrated by Vincenzo Peruggia. For 10 points, name this 1911 incident in which a painting by Leonardo da Vinci was stolen from the Louvre.", "answer": "<b><u>theft</u></b> of the <em><b><u>Mona Lisa</u></b></em> [accept equivalent answers saying the Mona Lisa was stolen]  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em>An early Christmas Day air raid during this war targeted an enemy fleet docked at Cuxhaven.</em> During this war, pamphlets in the colors of the Italian flag were dropped over Vienna by Gabriele (<b>pr. gah-bree-AY-lay</b>) d'Annunzio. This war's Battle of Arras (<b>pr. uh-RAH</b>) was known as \"Bloody April\" to the British. The first major wartime use of zeppelins and Fokker aircraft occurred during this conflict. For 10 points, name this war in which the Red Baron shot down over eighty enemy planes.", "answer": "<b><u>World War I</u></b> [or the <b><u>First World War</u></b>; prompt on the <b><u>Great War</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "KG"}, {"question": "<em>This man left his position as Chief Qadi of the Maldives after locals ignored his complaints</em> <em>about women going topless</em>. This man helped return the wife of Ozbeg Khan to her home city of Constantinople. After leaving the service of Muhammad bin Tughluq, this man visited the Yuan Dynasty capital of Khanbaliq before returning to his hometown of Tangier. For 10 points, name this 14th century Moroccan who documented his travels across much of Asia and Africa.", "answer": "<b><u>Ibn Battuta</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "TR"}, {"question": "<em>Francis Dana declined to join the main group in this event.</em> Pierre Bellamy suggested during this event that people make purchases at inflated prices. After this event, a man privately met with Elbridge Gerry at a dinner, seeking to separate him from his confederates. During it, Charles Pinckney reportedly said \"no, no, not a sixpence!\" to Talleyrand's agents. For 10 points, name this 1797 event in which three anonymous French diplomats seemingly requested a bribe from Americans.", "answer": "The <b><u>XYZ</u></b> Affair  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>This man was the executive president of the Russell Tribunal, which investigated American</em> <em>war crimes in Vietnam.</em> This man called Che Guevara \u201cthe most complete human being of our age,\u201d and wrote a preface to Frantz Fanon\u2019s anti-colonial <em>The Wretched Of the Earth.</em> This former POW of the Germans described his philosophy as \"a humanism\u201d in one lecture after he developed the concept of \u201cbad faith.\u201d For 10 points, name this existentialist philosopher of <em>Being</em> <em>and Nothingness.</em>", "answer": "Jean-Paul <b><u>Sartre</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "CW"}, {"question": "<em>During this conflict, an outlaw known as \"Five-Fingered Jack\" tortured Cowie and Fowler to</em> <em>death.</em> This conflict was ended by the arrival of John Sloat's squadron. During this conflict, Mariano Vallejo (<b>pr. vye-YAY-ho</b>) was arrested by a party led by \"Stuttering Zeke\" Merritt and William Ide. This rebellion occurred in Sonoma and was encouraged by the \"Pathfinder,\" John C. Fremont. For 10 points, name this 1846 revolt in California that adopted a grizzly as its symbol.", "answer": "<b><u>Bear Flag</u></b> Revolt  {I}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>Some members of the losing side in this battle fled to Evagoras.</em> Philocles was killed at this battle, from which the ship Paralus brought news of one side\u2019s defeat. The losers in this battle had their base at Sestos, following Alcibiades' advice, and were killed in a surprise attack while foraging. Conon survived this battle, in which the Delian League lost 170 triremes. For 10 points, name this decisive battle which was won by Lysander, ending the Peloponnesian War.", "answer": "Battle of <b><u>Aegospotami</u> </b>", "metadata": "History - Ancient History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>Cubs outfielder Rick Monday prevented people from doing this action at a 1976 game</em>. Gregory Lee Johnson was arrested for performing this action at the 1984 Republican National Convention. It was protected as free speech in the case <em>Texas v. Johnson</em>, which prompted William Rehnquist to decry attacks on \"the visible symbol embodying our Nation.\"For 10 points, name this action which involves symbolic, incendiary destruction of an iconic object.", "answer": "<b><u>burning</u></b> the American <b><u>flag</u></b> [accept obvious descriptions]", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>Karl Bischoff is best known for supervising an expansion in construction at this location.</em> Memories of this place inspired logotherapy, a type of existential psychotherapy developed by Viktor Frankl. The Monowitz facility expanded this place, where new people were brought to the \"ramp.\" This was the largest place with an entry gate displaying the message \"Arbeit macht frei\". For 10 points, name this site in Poland, which executed more people than any other Nazi death camp.", "answer": "<b><u>Auschwitz</u></b>-Birkenau [or Auschwitz II-<b><u>Birkenau</u></b>]", "metadata": "Social Science - Social Science - Psychology"}, {}, {"question": "<em>Many of this act\u2019s powers were removed in the Financial Services Modernization Act, or the</em> <em>Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act.</em> This act created an organization that pooled money from various banks to insure deposits, the FDIC. Paul Krugman claims its partial repeal in 1999 made the markets vulnerable to the 2008 financial crisis. A former Treasury Secretary was one of its two namesake Senate cosponsors. For 10 points, name this emergency 1933 act that cushioned the impact from bank failures.", "answer": "<b><u>Glass-Steagall</u></b> Act [or <b><u>Banking Act of 1933</u></b> until \u201c1933\u201d]", "metadata": "Current Events - Current Events"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This conflict began after the capture of the ship Tacuari.</em> Rutherford B. Hayes helped to arbitrate the treaty ending this conflict. The losing leader in this conflict was killed at the Battle of Cerro Cora, but his Irish mistress Eliza Lynch lived. The naval battle of Riachuelo was fought during it. At this war's star, one side was led by Bartolome Mitre against Francisco Solano Lopez. For 10 points, name this war in which Paraguay was defeated by a namesake coalition.", "answer": "War of the <b><u>Triple Alliance</u></b> [prompt on <b><u>Paraguayan</u></b> war until Paraguay]", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>James Covey was used by Willard Gibbs as a translator in this case</em>. Thomas Gedney sought salvage rights in this event, and Celestino and Ramon Ferrer were killed by forces led by Cinque in it. In the case caused by this event, Henry Gilpin\u2019s argument was defeated by Roger Baldwin, and the majority opinion was written by Joseph Story. For 10 points, name this incident where the Taney (<b>pr. TAW-nee</b>) Court ruled in favor of a group of slaves who mutinied on a namesake Cuban ship.", "answer": "<b><u>Amistad</u></b> affair [accept event, case, etc. for affair]", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>In 1934, Lithuanian-born noble Boris Skossyeff tried to declare himself King Boris I of this</em> <em>nation.</em> A series of medieval agreements called <em>par\u00e9ages</em>, starting in 1278, still determine the status of this country. A miter hat in the upper left of its coat of arms represents the Bishop of Urgell, a <em>de jure</em> leader of this country in tandem with a secular President of the country to its northeast. For 10 points, name this principality in the Pyrenees between Spain and France.", "answer": "Principality of <b><u>Andorra</u></b> [or Principat d'<b><u>Andorra</u></b>]", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This man lost his position as secretary of state after the assassination of Concino Concini.</em> This man married off his niece to the nephew of the \u201cgreat\u201d Cond\u00e9 the year before he was targeted by the conspiracy of Cinq-Mars. This man was targeted by the Day of the Dupes, which was orchestrated by Marie de M\u00e9dici. He besieged La Rochelle, the last Huguenot stronghold. For 10 points, name this cardinal who served as chief minister to King Louis XIII.", "answer": "Armand-Jean du <b><u>Plessis</u></b>, cardinal et duc de <b><u>Richelieu</u></b> [accept either underlined name; prompt on <b><u>Red Eminence</u></b> or <b><u>Eminence Rouge</u></b>]", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>His debut single was inspired by the story of a twelve-year-old putting her child in a trash</em> <em>compactor.</em> He dedicated one song to a 15-year-old whose murder helped spark the L.A. riots, Latasha Harlins. This artist of \u201cBrenda\u2019s Got A Baby\u201d and \u201cKeep Ya Head Up\u201d boasted that he\u2019s \u201cout on bail/fresh outta jail\u201d in another song, whose chorus boasts that his state \u201cknow\u2019s how to party\u201d. For 10 points, what rapper of \u201cCalifornia Love\u201d was murdered while riding in a car with Suge Knight and feuded with the Notorious B.I.G.?", "answer": "<b><u>Tupac</u></b> Shakur [or Tupac Amaru <b><u>Shakur</u></b>] [or Leshane Parish <b><u>Crooks</u></b>]", "metadata": "Trash - Trash"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This man is the subject of the documentary An Unreasonable Man</em>.This writer analyzed the \"Powerglide\" transmission in a groundbreaking book featuring the chapter \"Disaster deferred.\" This man's student task force, his namesake \"raiders,\" wrote reports attacking government corruption. He critiqued the Corvair in his 1965 book <em>Unsafe at Any Speed</em>.For 10 points, name this two time Green Party presidential nominee, a consumer protection advocate.", "answer": "Ralph <b><u>Nader</u> </b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>Lobbying on this man's behalf prevented Lewis Strauss from getting a Cabinet position</em>. This man had his security clearance and connections to the AEC suspended in 1953 on suspicion of his Communist sympathies. After seeing the Trinity test in New Mexico, he remarked \"Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds.\" For 10 points, name this scientist who headed the secret weapons laboratory as part of the Manhattan Project that made the atomic bomb.", "answer": "Julius Robert <b><u>Oppenheimer</u> </b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>The final verse of one of this author\u2019s poems exhorts \u201cShake your chains to earth like</em> <em>dew...Ye are many, they are few.\u201d</em> This author's poetic response to the Peterloo Massacre is titled <em>The Masque of Anarchy.</em> The speaker of another poem by this author meets \u201ca traveller from an antique land,\u201d who tells of a pedestal in the desert that says \u201cLook on my works, ye Mighty, and despair!\u201d For 10 points, name this British Romantic poet who used an alternate name of Rameses II to title his \"Ozymandias.\"<em>.</em>", "answer": "Percy Bysshe <b><u>Shelley</u> </b>", "metadata": "Literature - British Literature - Poetry"}, {}, {"question": "<em><b><u>In the last stages of this battle, Jean Auguste Margueritte led a failed cavalry charge on</u></b></em> <em><b><u>Floing.</u> </b></em><b><u>This battle was preceded by the Battle of Beaumont. Fighting in this battle began at</u></b> <b><u>Bazeilles (</u></b><u>pr. buh-ZAY</u><b><u>). During this battle, one side faced brief confusion over whether</u></b> <b><u>Auguste-Alexandre Ducrot or General Wimpffen was supposed to take charge of the Army</u></b> <b><u>of (+)</u>Chalons. In this battle, General MacMahon's forces were defeated by those of (*) </b>Helmuth von Moltke, leading to the capture of Napoleon III. For 10 points, name this decisive battle in the Franco-Prussian War.", "answer": "Battle of <b><u>Sedan</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>These objects were built by the Ruckers family of Antwerp.</u> </b></em><b><u>During the French Revolution,</u></b> <b><u>these objects were burned for firewood at the Paris Conservatoire. The muselaar was a</u></b> <b><u>small variety of this instrument. The firm of Pleyel and Co. custom-built one of these for</u></b> <b><u>Wanda (+)</u>Landowska, who revived it in the early 20th century. A treatise on this instrument was written by (*)</b> Francois Couperin. It has plectrums traditionally made out of quills, and its lack of dynamic contrast eventually led to its obsolescence in favor of the piano. For 10 points, name this Baroque keyboard instrument with plucked strings.", "answer": "<b><u>harpsichord</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "CW"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>The developer of the indigo industry, Eliza Lucas, married a member of this family.</u></b></em><b><u> Along</u></b> <b><u>with Pierce Butler, a politician from this family devised the Fugitive Slave Clause during</u></b> <b><u>the Constitutional Convention. A prominent member of this family was the (+)</u>Federalist candidate in the Presidential Elections of 1804 and 1808. Another politician with this surname negotiated free navigation of the (*)</b> Mississippi River in an agreement also called the Treaty of San Lorenzo. For 10 points, name this South Carolinian family, whose members included the namesake of a treaty that was signed with Spain.", "answer": "<b><u>Pinckney</u> </b> {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>Pamphlets inciting these wars accused one side of early uses of waterboarding on alleged</u></b></em> <em><b><u>perpetrators of the Amboyna massacre.</u></b></em><b><u> News of the secret Treaty of Dover re-started these</u></b> <b><u>conflicts, whose first and second examples ended with treaties negotiated by (+)</u>Johan de Witt. They weren't in Ireland, but the first one was the main foreign war launched by (*) </b>Oliver Cromwell, in response to piracy of merchant ships by a Calvinist republic. For 10 points, name these 17th-century wars between countries which later unified under Queen Mary and William III of Orange.", "answer": "<b><u>Anglo-Dutch</u></b> wars [accept any answer indicating conflicts between the kingdom of <b><u>England</u></b> and the <b><u>Netherlands</u></b>, <b><u>United Provinces</u></b>, <b><u>Dutch</u></b> Republic, etc.]  {II}", "metadata": "MJ"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>This religion celebrates a festival named for the garden where its founder announced he</u></b></em> <em><b><u>was a prophet.</u></b></em><b><u> That festival of this religion is the Ridv\u00e1n. The founder of this religion gave</u></b> <b><u>his first wife the title \u201cThe Most Exalted Leaf\u201d</u><u>and was succeeded by (+)</u>his son, Abbas Effendi. After being banished to Acre, that founder also wrote this religion\u2019s (*)</b> Book of Certitude and founded its first Houses of Justice. The forerunner of this religion, who adopted a name meaning \u201cgateway,\u201d was the Bab. For 10 points, name this religion founded by Baha\u2019ullah.", "answer": "<b><u>Baha\u2019i</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>The Manifesto of the 121 was written in response to this war.</u> </b></em><b><u>Gillo Pontecorvo is best</u></b> <b><u>known for directing a film set during this war. One side in this war made use of farmers</u></b> <b><u>called</u> </b><em><b><u>felleghas</u></b></em><b><u> in the Battle of Philippeville. This war resulted in the emigration of many</u></b> <b><u>(+)</u> Pieds-noirs. After torture reports surfaced, Jacques Massu was relieved from leading one side in this war. The (*) </b>Evian Accords ended this war, which was led on one side by the nationalistic party FLN. For 10 points, name this war in which an African nation gained independence from France.", "answer": "<b><u>Algerian War</u></b> of Independence [or <b><u>Algerian Revolution</u></b>; do not accept \"Algerian Civil War\"]  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>Grover Whalen was the president of this event, which was held on top of a former ash dump.</u> </b></em><b><u>One building in this event included a diorama entitled \u201cDemocracity,\u201d and Maurice</u></b> <b><u>Ascalon designed a sculpture here for the (+)</u>Jewish Palestine Pavilion. Johns Mansville promoted asbestos as the \u201cmagic mineral\u201d here. One exhibition in this event was designed by (*)</b> Norman Bel Geddes and imagined a system of automated highways. General Motors sponsored the Futurama exhibit here, and its symbol was the Trylon and Perisphere. For 10 points, what Depression-era exposition was held, like the 1964-1965 version, in Queens\u2019 Flushing Meadows?", "answer": "19<b><u>39</u></b>-1940 <b><u>World\u2019s Fair</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "CW"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>In the 2000's, several political parties in this non-U.S. country joined together to form the</u></b></em> <em><b><u>National Rainbow Coalition.</u> </b></em><b><u>The first president of this country followed a doctrine of</u></b> <b><u>\"pulling together\" called (+)</u>Harambee. To challenge this country's ruling political party, FORD was created by Luo chieftain Oginga Odinga. This country's second leader was (*) </b>Daniel arap Moi, who discriminated against this country's Kikuyu people. The Mau Mau uprising took place in this country. For 10 points, name this African country, whose first president was Jomo Kenyatta.", "answer": "<b><u>Kenya</u></b>  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>Ademar de Chabannes recorded an incident in which an unruly count asked this man</u></b></em> <em><b><u>\u201cWho made you king?\u201d</u></b></em><b><u> Pope John XV rejected this king\u2019s proposal to name Gerbert of</u></b> <b><u>Aurillac the Archbishop of Reims. This man was crowned in Noyon Cathedral after the</u></b> <b><u>death of (+)</u>Louis V in a hunting accident. This husband of Adelaide of Aquitaine pushed for the coronation of his son (*)</b> Robert the Pious early in his reign to secure succession in his newly founded dynasty. For 10 points, name this French king who founded a namesake royal house in 987.", "answer": "<b><u>Hugh</u></b> Capet  {II}", "metadata": "CKM"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>Giacomo Pilarino and Emanuel Timoni wrote letters describing this practice in the</u></b></em> <em><b><u>Ottoman Empire.</u> </b></em><b><u>Zabdiel Boylston observed empirical results of this practice in</u></b> <b><u>Massachusetts. Charles Maitland used this practice on the children of (+)</u>Lady Montagu, who spread it throughout Europe. A man who carried out this practice used lesions on the (*)</b> dairymaid Sarah Nelms and injected them into James Phipps. That form of this practice used cowpox. For 10 points, name this medical practice popularized by Edward Jenner, which conferred immunity against a viral disease.", "answer": "<b><u>inoculation</u></b> against <b><u>smallpox</u></b> [or <b><u>variolation</u></b> against <b><u>smallpox</u></b>; or <b><u>vaccination</u> </b>against <b><u>smallpox</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>The pseudonyms \"Cabu\" and \"Tignous\" were used by two members of this profession</u></b></em> <em><b><u>who had careers working for Stephane Charbonnier.</u></b></em><b><u> A 2009 book by Brandeis professor</u></b> <b><u>Jytte Clausen had the work of a man in this profession excised due to a last-minute decision</u></b> <b><u>by (+)</u>Yale University Press. Kurt Westegaard was one of these people targeted after a 2005 controversy involving the (*)</b><em>Jyllands-Posten</em> newspaper in Denmark. For 10 points, name these people who were targeted in early 2015 at the <em>Charlie Hebdo</em> newspaper for their offensive depictions of Muhammad.", "answer": "political <b><u>cartoonist</u></b>s [or <b><u>artist</u></b>s; or <b><u>illustrator</u></b>s; prompt on <b><u>satirist</u></b>s, <b><u>comedian</u></b>s, or other answers that don't directly indicate the production of imagines]  {II}", "metadata": "MJ"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>A TV movie about this group resulted in Ruby Bates suing for being called a prostitute</u></b></em><b><u>.</u></b> <b><u>While working for this group, Samuel Leibowitz proclaimed his trust in the \"God fearing</u></b> <b><u>people of Decatur.\" Victoria Price's accusations about this group used details from a (+)</u> </b><em><b>Saturday Evening Post </b></em><b>work of fiction. They were arrested in Paint Rock after being found \"hoboing\" on a freight train. This group's (*) </b>conviction was voided in the Supreme Court case <em>Powell v. Alabama</em>.For 10 points, name this group of nine black teenagers accused of raping two white women in 1931.", "answer": "<b><u>Scottsboro</u></b> Boys [or <b><u>Scottsboro</u></b> Nine]  {II}  <b>Extra Tossup</b> This is a tossup provided for breaking ties or replacing a flubbed or erroneous question at any point in the packet. The power marks are provided so that it may be scored according to fourth quarter rules if it is replacing a fourth quarter question. The power marks should be ignored if this tossup is used to replace a first or second quarter question.", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>A member of this family failed to commute the execution of Caryl Chessman</u></b></em><b><u>. A member</u></b> <b><u>of this family was known as \"Moonbeam\" while he dated Linda Ronstadt. That member</u></b> <b><u>served in his highest position when Howard Jarvis pushed through the (+)</u>property tax slashing Proposition 13. Another member of this family defeated Richard Nixon in a 1962 election, but lost to (*)</b> Ronald Reagan a few years later. That member of this family, Pat, was governor of his state during the Watts Riots. For 10 points, name this family of California Governor Jerry.", "answer": "<b><u>Brown</u></b> [or Edmund Gerald \u201cPat\u201d <b><u>Brown</u></b>; or Edmund Gerald \u201cJerry\u201d <b><u>Brown</u></b> Jr.]  {II}", "metadata": "MC"}], "bonuses": []}